Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A family group of nine, seated around a rustic wooden table under a wooden shade. Ottoman writing on the back in pencil., 1925 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Family; Family Portraits; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints
- Two older females in light skirt suits in front of some bushes and trees. Turkish writing in black ink., August 1938 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkish Writing; Women
- An older male with a young girl standing between his legs in an outdoor courtyard. Turkish writing in pencil on the back., 7 September 1934 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Photographic Prints
- A young male on one knee in front of a building. Turkish writing in blue ink on reverse. Blue ink has bled on front and back of photograph., undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A family group of three, a young male stands behind an older couple. Mazhar Ruster, Izmir, Turkey. Turkish writing in blue ink., 8 April 1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Family Portraits; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A female sitting on the beach in a cover-up. A van with a popped hood in the background., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Beach; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Van, Turkey
- A group of six young children. Boy in front row is holding an accordion., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Children; Group Portraits; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints
- Two females in fancy dress. Studio Yanyeri., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Party; Photographic Prints; Women
- A large group of mixed males and females, standing in an alcove of a delapidated church, murals in the background., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
- A group of five people gathered around a desk with some flowers on it, two men in military uniform., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Gatherings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- A group of older five women and four children posing in in front of some trees., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
- A man with crossed arms in a light suit, standing in front of a large group of children and adult onlookers., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Children; Crowd; Photographic Prints
- Two couples sitting in front of a fountain with outdoor tables around them, in a hotel., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Couple; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
- Four older women sitting in a garden in front of a house. Woman on far left is wearing a scarf., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
- A family group of five in a bedroom with wallpaper, young male has a gun in a holster on his waist., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Beds; Group Portraits; Newspapers; Photographic Prints
- A group of men in suits looking at a male putting a ring on a woman's finger., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Gatherings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
- A birthday party with young children and their mothers. Birthday boy is leaning over the table to blow out the candles., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Children; Eating; Group Portraits; Party; Photographic Prints; Women
- Five women sitting on a bed, one has a scarf wrapped around her head., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Beds; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group at a wedding with the bride and groom standing in the middle, in front of three large flower arrangements., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Family Portraits; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Portraits
- A group of eight women posing on the lawn in front of a house., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- A class of children all in the same school uniform, teacher is in the middle back row., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Children; Photographic Prints; Schools
- Two men and three women. Two women have their head covered with a scarf., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Two boys laying in bed, an older man in a suit is leaning over the boy in the background., 6 May 1942 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Beds; Boys; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A couple, female is wearing a light top and has short hair. Foto Sens., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Three adults and two children, standing on a dirt road with trees in the background., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Family; Nature; Photographic Prints
- A young girl in aprons, holding teacups at a table set for a meal., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Tea
- A group of school girls in uniform posing outside a building with white bars on the windows, teacher standing on the far left., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools
- A couple, female is wearing a white dress with dark flowers on it., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
- A boy holding younger sibling, undated
  Children; Crowd; Family; Photographic Prints; Streets
- ref1301
- ref1302
- ref1303
- ref1304
- ref1305
- ref1306
- ref1307
- ref1308
- ref1309